# **FAZA DANDY A**

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

0896854345331 | fazadandyakmalin0@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/faza-dandy

Jombang, Jawa Timur, Indonesia

A graduate of Vocational High School in Computer Network Engineering. Experienced as a Front-End Developer who works with HTML, CSS, JavaScript. Currently working as a Front-End Developer and also attending Full-Stack Web Developer bootcamp program for deepening skills in Web Developer. A detail-oriented individual who is eager for a full-time opportunity in Full-Stack Web Development.

### Work Experience

PT. Jajag Mitra Usaha - Jombang, Indonesia

Dec, 2022 - Mar 2023

Music App Developer Intern

- Developed a Music App compliant with accessibility standards, policies, and procedures.
- Developed and maintained the application to ensure its smooth performance.
- Developed the app using Andromo.

### **Project Experiences**

Music App - PT. Jajag Mitra Usaha

Dec. 2022 - Mar 2023

Music App Developer

- Developed the Music app using Andromo with the team.
- Created the Music app for the Google Play Store.

### **Education Level**

SMK Budi Utomo - Jombang, Indonesia

2018 - 2021

Graduate of Vocational High School in Computer Network Engineering

- Thesis: A Sustainable Project-based Learning Methodology for Web Programming
- Relevant Course Works: Database, Web Development, System, HTML, and JavaScript

## **Courses, Training and Certifications**

FreeCodeCamp.org - San Francisco, California, United States

May, 2023 - July, 2023

Responsive Web Design, 3.54/4.00

- Final Project: Build a Personal Portfolio Webpage
- Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Certificate:

Harisenin.com - Jakarta, Indonesia

Feb, 2024 - Present

Full Stack Developer Bootcamp, 3.54/4.00

- Final Project: Designed and developed a website for an insurance company, Insurance Technology, within three months
- Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Native and Node.js
- Certificate:

#### Skills

Technical skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Git, Github, Andromo

Soft skills: Problem Solving, Time Management, Orientation to Detail, Analytical Thinking and Teamwork

Languages: Indonesian (Native), English (Beginner)

2010 - 20